Charles Werner Papers
Charles Werner Papers
1938-1966
Werner, Charles George, 1909-1997.
7.9 linear feet
909 original cartoons, proofs, correspondence, printed material and biographic information.
2642901
Biographical History
Charles George Werner (1909-1997) was a Pulitzer Prize winning American cartoonist who worked for the Indianapolis Star for 47 years.
Charles Werner was born March 23, 1909 in Marshfield, Wisconsin to George and Marie (Tipelt) Werner. Werner attended Oklahoma City University but had no formal training in art. He worked as a staff artist and photographer for the Springfield, Missouri Leader and Press from 1930 until 1935. He joined the staff of the Daily Oklahoman in 1935, becoming editorial cartoonist in 1937.
Werner won the Pulitzer Prize for Editorial Cartooning in 1939 for a cartoon he did for the Daily Oklahoman titled “Nomination for 1938” which appeared on October 6, 1938. The cartoon commented on the Munich Agreement which allowed for the transfer of the Sudetenland to Hitler's Germany. At age 29, Werner was the youngest person to win the Pulitzer in that category.
Werner left the Daily Oklahoman to be the Chief Editorial Cartoonist at the Chicago Sun in 1941 before leaving for the Indianapolis Star in 1947 where he stayed until his retirement in 1994. Werner received a Sigma Delta Chi Award for excellence in journalism in 1943 and seven Freedom Foundation Awards from 1951 to 1963. At the 1969 International Salon of Cartoons in Montreal, he won an award as one of the world's six best cartoonists. In 1959 and 1960, Werner served as the president of the Association of American Editorial Cartoonists.
Throughout his nearly sixty year career, many U.S. Presidents expressed interest in Werner's cartoons. In 1965, Lyndon B. Johnson requested over a dozen original cartoons from Werner for his personal collection. Former President Harry Truman also requested a cartoon for his presidential library.
Charles Werner died on July 1, 1997 from cancer.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Charles Werner Papers consists of five series: Cartoons (1947-1965), Proofs (1959-1964), Correspondence (1938-1964), Biographical material and Printed material.
The bulk of the collection is 909 editorial cartoons drawn by Werner for the Indianapolis Star located in the Cartoons series. Werner considered himself a conservative and often depicted the influence of big government as evidenced in his portrayal of President Harry Truman continuing on the liberal, tax and spend path of predecessor Franklin Roosevelt and the problems of too over involvement in foreign affairs. He also used sports motifs to portray political issues. Werner frequently commented on high rates of automobile accident deaths. His attention to this issue won him an award from National Foundation for Highway Safety.
Dimensions vary but most of the cartoons are approximately 11 1/4 x 13 3/4". Some of the original cartoons have newspaper clippings of the cartoon taped on the back. The cartoons were drawn on coquille board with ink and graphite.
Several years of proofs are included in the collection.
Correspondence contains incoming and outgoing correspondence. Correspondents included: professional organizations, elected officials including Barry Goldwater and Harry Truman (the letter is undated but is from after Truman's presidency), fans and fellow cartoonists including Carey Orr and Milton Caniff.
The biographical material and printed material series contain assorted information related to Werner's career and awards; articles and clippings about Werner; a handful of photographs and examples of his work syndicated outside of the United States.
Arrangement of the Collection
Cartoons and proofs are arranged in chronological order by month. Correspondence is arranged and foldered by year.
Related Material
has collections of over one hundred cartoonists. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Dwight David), 1890-1969 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Werner, Charles George, 1909-1997.; Indianapolis star.; United States. Congress -- Caricatures and cartoons.; United Nations -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Art -- Cartoonists; American wit and humor, Pictorial.; Caricatures and cartoons -- United States.; Cold War -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Communism -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Cartoonists -- United States.; Editorial cartoons -- Indiana.; Editorial cartoons -- United States.; Political cartoons.; Taxation -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Traffic fatalities -- Caricatures and cartoons.; World politics -- 1945-1989 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Cartoons (humorous images); Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Editorial cartoons.; Printers' proofs.; Cartoonists.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Charles Werner, 1965 and 1967.
Inventory
- Cartoons, See below for an index to the cartoons.
  - 1947 Jan- 1947 Jul, 10 items (Oversize 1, Folder 1)
  - 1947 Aug - 1947 Dec, 11 items (Oversize 1, Folder 2)
  - 1948 Jan - 1948 Mar, 14 items (Oversize 1, Folder 3)
  - 1948 Apr - 1948 Jun, 13 items (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
  - 1948 Jul - 1948 Oct, 13 items (Oversize 1, Folder 5)
  - 1948 Nov - 1948 Dec, 8 items (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
  - 1949 Jan - 1949 May, 12 items (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
  - 1949 Jun - 1949 Jul, 14 items (Oversize 1, Folder 8)
  - 1949 Aug - 1949 Oct, 13 items (Oversize 1, Folder 9)
  - 1949 Nov - 1949 Dec, 6 items (Oversize 1, Folder 10)
  - 1950 Jan - 1950 Feb, 12 items (Oversize 1, Folder 11)
  - 1950 Mar - 1950 Sep, 14 items (Oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - 1950 Oct - 1950 Dec, 13 items (Oversize 2, Folder 2)
  - 1951 Jan, 1951 Mar - 1951 May, 10 items (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
  - 1951 Jun - 1951 Oct, 10 items (Oversize 2, Folder 4)
  - 1951 Nov - 1951 Dec, 13 items (Oversize 2, Folder 5)
  - 1952 Jan - 1952 Feb, 15 items (Oversize 2, Folder 6)
  - 1952 Mar - 1952 May, 14 items (Oversize 2, Folder 7)
  - 1952 Jun - 1952 Aug, 13 items (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
  - 1952 Sep - 1952 Oct, 11 items (Oversize 2, Folder 9)
  - 1952 Nov - 1952 Dec, 7 items (Oversize 3, Folder 1)
  - 1953 Feb - 1953 May, 11 items (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
  - 1953 Jun - 1953 Aug, 9 items (Oversize 3, Folder 3)
  - 1953 Sep, 9 items (Oversize 3, Folder 4)
  - 1953 Oct - 1953 Nov, 16 items (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
  - 1953 Dec, 4 items (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
  - 1954 Jan - 1954 Feb, 8 items (Oversize 3, Folder 7)
  - 1954 Mar - 1954 May, 8 items (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
  - 1954 Sep- Oct; 1954 Dec, 5 items (Oversize 3, Folder 9)
  - 1955 Jan - 1955 Apr, 10 items (Oversize 3, Folder 10)
  - 1955 May - 1955 Sep, 14 items (Oversize 4, Folder 1)
  - 1955 Oct - 1955 Dec, 11 items (Oversize 4, Folder 2)
  - 1956 Jan - 1956 May, 12 items (Oversize 4, Folder 3)
  - 1956 Jun - 1956 Oct, contains 1 color cartoon drawn in watercolor and ink; 12 items (Oversize 4, Folder 4)
  - 1956 Nov - 1956 Dec, 8 items (Oversize 4, Folder 5)
  - 1957 Jan - 1957 Feb, 15 items (Oversize 4, Folder 6)
  - 1957 Mar - 1957 May, 22 items (Oversize 4, Folder 7)
  - 1957 Jun - 1957 Jul, 14 items (Oversize 4, Folder 8)
  - 1957 Aug - 1957 Sep, 15 items (Oversize 4, Folder 9)
  - 1957 Oct - 1957 Dec, 11 items (Oversize 4, Folder 10)
  - 1958 Jan - 1958 Apr, 1958 Jun - 1958 Jul, 13 items (Oversize 5, Folder 1)
  - 1958 Aug - 1958 Dec, 16 items (Oversize 5, Folder 2)
  - 1959 Jan - 1959 Mar, 10 items (Oversize 5, Folder 3)
  - 1959 May - 1959 Jul, 14 items (Oversize 5, Folder 4)
  - 1959 Aug, 1959 Oct - 1959 Dec, 8 items (Oversize 5, Folder 5)
  - 1960 Jan - 1960 Feb, 13 items (Oversize 5, Folder 6)
  - 1960 Apr - 1960 May, 11 items (Oversize 5, Folder 7)
  - 1960 Jun - 1960 Aug, 14 items (Oversize 5, Folder 8)
  - 1960 Sep - 1960 Oct, 14 items (Oversize 5, Folder 9)
  - 1960 Nov - 1960 Dec, 8 items (Oversize 5, Folder 10)
  - 1961 Jan - 1961 Apr, 12 items (Oversize 6, Folder 1)
  - 1961 May - 1961 Sep, 12 items (Oversize 6, Folder 2)
  - 1961 Nov - 1961 Dec, 9 items (Oversize 6, Folder 3)
  - 1960 Jan - 1960 Mar, 17 items (Oversize 6, Folder 4)
  - 1960 Apr - 1960 Jul, 15 items (Oversize 6, Folder 5)
  - 1962 Aug - 1962 Sep, 12 items (Oversize 6, Folder 6)
  - 1962 Oct - 1962 Dec, 10 items (Oversize 6, Folder 7)
  - 1963 Jan - 1963 Mar, 10 items (Oversize 6, Folder 8)
  - 1963 Apr - 1963 May, 12 items (Oversize 6, Folder 9)
  - 1963 Jun 1963 Aug, 10 items (Oversize 6, Folder 10)
  - 1963 Sep - 1963 Oct, 11 items (Oversize 7, Folder 1)
  - 1963 Nov - 1963 Dec, 13 items (Oversize 7, Folder 2)
  - 1964 Jan, 21 items (Oversize 7, Folder 3)
  - 1964 Feb, 11 items (Oversize 7, Folder 4)
  - 1964 Mar, 13 items (Oversize 7, Folder 5)
  - 1964 Apr, 19 items (Oversize 7, Folder 6)
  - 1964 May, 13 items (Oversize 7, Folder 7)
  - 1964 Jun, 15 items (Oversize 7, Folder 8)
  - 1964 Jul, 12 items (Oversize 8, Folder 1)
  - 1964 Aug, 9 items (Oversize 8, Folder 2)
  - 1964 Sep, 12 items (Oversize 8, Folder 3)
  - 1964 Oct, 24 items (Oversize 8, Folder 4)
  - 1964 Nov, 12 items (Oversize 8, Folder 5)
  - 1964 Dec, 19 items (Oversize 8, Folder 6)
  - 1965; undated, 5 items (Oversize 8, Folder 7)
- Proofs, 8 ½" x 12"
  - 1959 Jan - 1959 Oct (Box 1)
  - 1960 Apr (Box 1)
  - 1960 Jul (Box 1)
  - 1960 Sep (Box 1)
  - 1960 Dec (Box 1)
  - 1961 Jan - 1961 Dec (Box 1)
  - 1962 Jan - 1962 Dec (Box 1)
  - 1963 Jan - 1963 Dec (Box 2)
  - 1964 Jan - 1964 Dec (Box 2)
- Correspondence
  - 1938-1945 (Box 2)
  - 1939 (Box 2)
  - 1940 (Box 2)
  - 1941 (Box 2)
  - 1942 (Box 2)
  - 1943 (Box 2)
  - 1944 (Box 2)
  - 1945 (Box 2)
  - 1947, 1950-1951, 1954-1955 (Box 2)
  - 1957-1958 (Box 2)
  - 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - 1964 (Box 2)
  - undated (Box 2)
- Biographical material
  - Biography; photographs, 1966; undated; includes photograph of Werner's Pulitzer Prize winning cartoon (Box 3)
  - Sigma Delta Chi Awards announcement (1961); Headliner Awards History (circa 1958 and 1959) (Box 3)
  - Award Winners for Editors and Cartoonists- National Foundation for Highway Safety, 1963; Werner's award winning cartoon is located in Box 7 Folder 2. (Box 3)
- Printed material
  - Tarantel Press (Berlin, Germany) syndication, undated; 14 examples of Werner's work in German (Box 3)
  - Quill and Scroll; Quill, Feb/Mar 1954; May 1957 (Box 3)
  - Editor and Publisher, 31 Oct 1959; 7 Nov 1959 (Box 3)
  - Clippings, 1963-1964; undated (Box 3)
Index to cartoons
The following is a list of predominant people, places and subjects appearing in the editorial cartoons in this collection. The list is not exhaustive. Some subjects may require you to browse with alternative terms.
B= Box, F= Folder. For example: B1F1= Box 1 Folder 1.
Acheson, Dean B2F5
AFL-CIO B2F2 B4F2 B4F4 B5F2
Alaska B3F2
Algeria B6F4 B6F9
anti-Semitism B5F6
Argentina B6F4
Asia B3F7-B3F8 B4F9 B7F7-B7F8 B8F4
Atlantic Pact B1F7-B1F9
Attlee, Clement B3F2
auto industry B2F2 B8F4
automobile accidents B1F2 B1F8 B2F1 B2F6 B3F2-B3F3 B3F9 B4F1-B4F2 B4F7 B4F10 B5F2 B5F7 B7F2 B8F3 B8F6
Batista, Fulgencio B6F2
beef industry B2F3-B2F4
Brannan Plan B1F8 B2F1
Brazil B7F2 B7F6
Brezhnev, Leonid Ilyich B8F6
Britain B2F7-B2F8 B3F3 B4F1 B4F7 B6F9-B6F10 B7F3
California B2F1 B5F1
Canada B6F5
cancer B1F4
capitalism B6F5
Carson, Rachel B7F6
Castro, Fidel B5F5 B5F9-B6F5 B6F8 B7F3-B7F4 B7F6 B8F2
Chamberlain, Neville B2F3
charity B4F2 B4F4
child support B2F4
China B1F6-B1F7 B1F10-B1F11 B2F2-B2F3 B2F5 B3F4-B3F5 B4F7 B4F9 B5F2 B5F4 B5F10-B6F1 B6F4-B6F5 B6F7 B7F6-B7F8 B8F2 B8F4
civil rights B1F3 B4F4 B4F8-B4F10 B5F6 B6F1 B6F5-B6F6 B6F9-B7F1 B7F6 B7F8-B8F1
Clark, Mark Wayne B2F8
coal industry B1F11 B3F1
Cold War B3F10 B4F2 B5F3 B5F8
collectivism B1F9
Colombia B1F3
communism B1F2-B1F4 B1F9 B1F11-B2F5 B3F1-B3F6 B3F8 B3F10-B4F2 B4F7 B4F9 B5F1 B5F7-B5F9 B6F2-B6F5 B6F7-B6F9 B7F3-B7F4 B7F6-B7F8 B8F5
Congo B5F8-B5F9 B6F1-B6F4 B6F6 B8F5
Congress B1F1 B1F3-B1F5 B1F8-B1F9 B1F11 B2F3 B2F6 B2F8 B3F7-B3F8 B4F2-B4F3 B4F6-B4F9 B5F1-B5F6 B5F8 B6F2 B6F6 B6F8 B6F10-B7F1 B7F3-B7F6 B8F5-B8F6
credit B1F1-B1F2 B2F7 B4F2
crime B3F5 B4F3 B4F6 B5F8 B6F4
Cuba B5F8-B5F9 B6F1 B6F4-B6F6 B6F8-B6F9 B7F3 B8F2
Czechoslovakia B1F3-B1F4
de Gaulle, Charles B5F6 B6F1 B6F10 B7F3
debt B4F1 B7F2 B7F8
deflation B1F3 B1F8
democracy B1F5-B1F6 B5F7
Democratic Party B1F4 B1F8 B2F3 B3F5 B3F7 B4F3-B4F4 B5F1 B5F3 B7F6 B8F3-B8F4
Dewey, Thomas B1F4 B2F2
Dirksen, Everett B8F1
disarmament B1F5 B2F5 B4F4 B4F8 B5F5 B7F6
Dixiecrats B1F6 B2F3
draft B4F6
drug use B1F5 B4F8
Dulles, John Foster B3F4 B4F7 B5F2
Duvalier, François B6F9-B6F10
economy B2F1 B2F6 B4F6-B4F7 B5F4 B6F1 B6F10 B7F5-B7F6
Eden, Anthony B4F5
schools B1F2 B1F5 B1F10 B2F8 B4F4 B5F8 B6F10 B8F3
Egypt B4F1 B4F6 B8F6
Eisenhower, Dwight B2F2 B2F4 B2F6-B3F1 B3F6-B3F8 B3F10-B4F1 B4F4-B4F5 B4F7-B5F2 B5F4-B5F5 B5F7-B5F9 B7F3 B8F1 B8F7
elections B1F3 B1F6 B2F6 B3F4 B3F7-B3F7 B3F10-B4F1 B4F3-B4F4 B5F2 B5F6-B5F10 B6F7 B7F3 B7F5 B7F8 B8F3
En-lai, Chou B7F3
Europe B1F1-B1F2 B4F3 B5F2 B5F6
farming B3F5 B3F10 B4F4 B4F9 B5F2 B5F4
Federal Bureau of Investigation B4F9
Finland B1F4
flooding B4F7 B5F3
Formosa B1F10-B1F11 B3F10 B5F2
France B2F6 B3F5 B3F9 B5F8 B6F1-B6F2 B6F4 B8F3
free press B3F8 B7F5
freedom B2F2 B5F4 B8F1
gambling B1F3 B2F2
Gandhi B1F3
Germany B1F6-B1F7 B1F11-B2F1 B2F6-B2F7 B3F4-B3F5 B3F9 B4F1 B4F10 B5F2 B5F4 B5F10 B6F4 B6F6 B6F9 B7F5-B7F6
Girard Case B4F8
Glenn, John B7F3
Goldberg, Arthur B6F5
Goldwater, Barry B6F9 B7F1-B7F3 B7F5 B7F7-B8F4 B8F6-B8F7
Grand Army of the Republic B1F9
Greece B7F5-B7F6 B8F2
Greenlease, Bobby B3F5
Haiti B6F9-B6F10
Harriman, W. Averell B4F3 B6F5
Hawaii B1F4 B1F9 B3F2 B5F3
Hoffa, Jimmy B6F7 B7F5 B8F1
holidays B1F1-B1F2 B1F7-B1F8 B2F5 B3F9 B4F2 B4F7 B4F10 B5F2 B6F9 B8F3 B8F5
Honduras B7F3
Hoover, Herbert B1F9 B8F4
Hoover, J. Edgar B8F6
Humphrey, Hubert B5F6-B5F7 B8F3-B8F4 CHECK SPELL
Hungary B2F5 B4F5 B5F3
hunger B1F2
Iceland B4F3
India B1F3 B2F4 B2F6 B3F1 B3F3 B6F7
Indiana B1F2 B1F5 B1F8 B2F1 B2F7 B3F5 B3F7 B4F6 B4F8 B5F5 B5F8 B6F7-B6F9 B7F4 B7F6-B7F7 B8F1-B8F2 B8F7
Indonesia B1F6
inflation B1F3 B2F1 B2F5-B2F6 B2F8 B4F6 B4F9 B6F1-B6F2 B8F4
Iran B2F3 B2F7
Iraq B5F4 B6F9
Islam B2F8 B6F10
Israel B4F6-B4F7
Japan B5F7 B5F8
Johnson, Lyndon Baines B5F1 B5F7 B7F2-B7F7 B8F1 B8F3-B8F7
Keating, Kenneth B8F3
Kennedy, John F. B5F6-B5F8 B6F1-B6F9 B7F1-B7F2
Kennedy, Robert F. B6F8 B8F3-B8F4
Kennedy, Ted B6F6
Khrushchev, Nikita B4F2 B5F2 B5F6-B6F8 B6F10 B7F3 B7F5-B7F6 B8F3 B8F5
Kishi, Nobusuke B5F8
Korean War B2F1-B2F6 B2F8-B3F5 B4F2 B5F1 B5F7
Kosygin, Alexey B8F6
Ku Klux Klan B6F10
labor B1F2 B4F7 B5F1 B6F10
Laos B6F1 B6F5 B7F7
Latin America B3F5 B6F1 B6F9 B7F1
Lewis, John B1F1 B1F4 B1F8 B1F10-B1F11 B5F5
liberty B1F3 B1F5-B1F6 B2F4
Lincoln, Abraham B3F10
MacArthur, Douglas B2F2-B2F3 B2F8 B7F6
MacMillan, Harold B5F3 B6F7
Malenkov, Georgy B3F2 B3F5
Marshall Plan B1F2-B1F3 B1F11
McCarthy, Joseph B3F8
McCarthyism B2F9
McNamara, Robert B5F10 B7F3 B7F5 B7F7 B8F4-B8F6
Medicare B6F5 B7F2
Memorial Day B1F1
Middle East B1F2 B4F4-B4F7 B4F10-B5F1 B5F4 B6F2
minimum wage B6F1
Molotov, Vyacheslav B1F5 B2F2
Munich Agreement B1F5
Nasser, Gamal Abdel B4F6 B6F9
NATO B3F8 B4F7
nature conservation B6F4
Nazism B1F3
Nebraska B1F4
Nehru, Jawaharlal B2F6 B3F3
Netherlands B1F6 B7F7
New York B5F3
Nixon, Richard M. B4F4 B5F1 B5F8-B5F9 B7F3 B8F7
nuclear weapons B1F9 B2F6 B3F4-B3F5 B3F8 B4F1 B4F3 B4F9 B5F1-B5F2 B5F6 B5F10 B6F4-B6F6 B6F10-B7F1 B8F4 B8F6
oil B2F3 B2F7 B6F2
Organization of American States B6F4 B7F4
Palestine B1F2 B1F5
Panama B7F3
peace B1F1-B1F3 B1F5 B1F7-B1F9 B1F11 B2F2-B2F7 B3F2-B3F7 B3F10 B4F3 B4F7
Peron, Juan Domingo B2F5 B4F1
Petrillo, James B1F6
Poland B1F4
Pope Pius XII B5F2
Potsdam Agreement B2F1
prices B3F1 B5F3 B6F1 B6F6 B6F9 B8F7
prosperity B1F5 B1F7 B8F4
Queen Elizabeth II B2F6 B3F3 B4F10
quiz shows B5F5
railroad industry B1F4-B1F5 B6F10 B7F6
record industry B1F6
religion B1F3 B5F4 B6F5 B7F3
Republican Party B1F1 B1F3-B1F5 B1F11 B2F3 B2F5 B2F7 B3F6-B3F7 B4F2-B4F5 B4F7 B5F1-B5F3 B5F8 B6F3 B7F3 B7F6-B8F1 B8F4-B8F6
Reuther, Walter B2F2 B5F4 B8F4
Rhee, Syngman B5F7
right to work law B4F6 B5F3
Rockefeller, Nelson B5F3 B5F8 B7F1-B7F2 B7F5 B7F7-B7F8 B8F7
Romney, George W. B7F1 B8F5 B8F7
Russia B1F1-B1F3 B1F5 B1F7 B1F9 B1F11-B2F1 B2F4 B3F2 B3F4 B3F7-B3F8 B3F10-B4F2 B4F5 B4F7-B4F8 B5F3 B5F7 B6F1 B6F6 B7F2-B7F4 B8F4
Saud, Ibn B5F1
Scranton, William B7F1 B7F8-B8F1 B8F5 B8F7
slums B3F10 B5F4
Smith, Margaret Chase B7F2-B7F3
socialism B1F8-B1F9 B2F4
socialized medicine B6F5 B7F6
soil and water management B4F7
South Carolina B1F1
South Korea B5F7
Soviet Union B1F4 B3F4 B4F3 B4F8 B5F2 B5F4 B6F6 B8F6
space exploration B4F10-B5F2 B6F4-B6F5 B6F8 B7F4 B8F4
sports B2F4-B2F5 B3F9 B4F1 B4F4 B5F2 B5F4 B6F7
Stalin, Joseph B1F5-B1F6 B1F8-B1F9 B2F1-B2F3 B2F6-B2F8 B3F1-B3F2 B8F5
Stassen, Harold B1F4 B2F5
steel industry B1F3 B2F5 B2F8 B5F4-B5F5 B6F2 B6F5-B6F6 B6F9 B8F7
Stevenson, Adlai B2F7 B2F9 B3F10 B4F3-B4F5 B5F7-B5F8 B6F3 B6F7 B8F6
strikes B1F1 B1F4 B2F7-B2F8 B6F2 B7F6
Supreme Court B2F3 B4F8 B5F4 B7F5
Symington, Stuart B5F6
Syria B6F9
Taft Hartley Act B1F2 B1F8 B1F10-B1F11 B2F7-B2F8 B5F5 B6F2 B6F7
Taft, Robert B2F7-B2F8
tariffs B1F9
taxes B1F1 B1F3 B1F7 B1F9-B2F2 B2F5 B3F1 B3F3 B3F5 B3F7-B3F8 B3F10 B4F3 B4F6-B4F9 B5F1 B5F3-B5F4 B5F6-B5F8 B5F10-B6F1 B6F5-B6F8 B7F1 B7F4 B7F7 B8F1 B8F4 B8F6
terrorism B1F2 B1F8 B2F7
Thant, U B6F3 B8F5
Thule Air Base B3F5
Tibet B2F4 B5F3-B5F4 B6F7
Tito, Josip Broz B6F7
Tobin, Dan B1F4
Truman, Harry S. B1F3-B2F4 B2F6-B3F1 B3F5 B4F1
Turkey B7F5-B7F6 B8F2
U.S. Constitution B2F1 B4F8
U.S. Mail B6F1
U.S. Treasury B1F1 B4F8
UFOs B2F1 B2F8
Ulbricht, Walter B6F2
unemployment B5F5
unions B1F2 B1F11 B2F7 B4F2 B4F6 B5F2 B5F4-B5F5 B7F5
United Nations B1F2-B1F3 B1F5 B1F9 B1F11-B2F3 B2F5 B2F9 B3F2 B3F4-B3F5 B3F9-B3F10 B4F5 B5F2 B5F4 B5F8-B6F6 B8F4-B8F6
universities B2F7
urban renewal B7F6
USS Thresher B6F9
Vietnam B4F1 B5F1 B7F1-B7F2 B7F7-B7F8 B8F5
Vishinsky, Andrey B2F5 B3F1
Wallace, George B7F1 B7F6 B8F1
war B1F7-B1F8 B2F2 B5F1 B5F4
War on Poverty B7F5 B8F5
Warren, Earl B4F8
weather B4F1 B5F6 B7F6 B8F2
white supremacy B1F3
Wilson, Charles E. B4F6 B4F9 B8F7
World War II B1F5
Zanzibar B7F3
Zedong, Mao B6F8 B7F3 B8F2